<resources>
    <string name="app_name">textScroll</string>
    <string name="article_heading">Article Title</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Article Subtitle</string>
    <string name="article_text">This is not my first Android App. But, I\'m still at my learning phase.\n\n Go to www.google.com for more info.\n\n I"'"m trying to figure out how Android Studio works. Over here we were asked to add text longer than our screen, so that we can add a scrolling option. But instead of copy pasting I am writing my own text for mine and others"'" convenience. I love developing apps and websites. It is quite fun and interesting. Though, I am having a bit of difficulties catching up in the lab, because of my own faults. I did get very demotivated in betwenn, but now I feel much better and I"'"m ready to work hard. Though this is just for a course, I have huge dreams in life. I have a really long way to go, and sometimes I forget that. Since I dont have anyone else to remind me of that, it does get hard sometimes. But Inn Sha Allah I know I can do better and I know I will achieve it one day. Thanks for reading. So it still didnt fill the screen, so I will keep writing gibberish now. lalalalalalalalalalalaalalallllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllalallalalaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaajhrjgrfewhchjbwhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
    jhjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjdnsckjdnvkjcbdsvh
    kjcklsfddn                         mcncjvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvv
    kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk                                                          ijfcwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww</string>
</resources>